Our next stretch is going to be a side stretch.
Let's go ahead and taking the hands by your side and stretching one side at a time we'll start with the right side inhaling up with the right arm.
Then you exhale and slowly take it over to the side.
You like to look up at your hand as you're stretching feeling it stretch and deepening the stretch along your side.
This bottom hand, every exhalation the elbow getting closer to the floor.
So as you inhale you lift, exhale dropping closer to the floor reaching the hand up towards the ceiling farther along to the side of the wall.
Inhale and exhale stretching deeper.
The next exhale you'll slowly bring it back to center and then do the same thing on the other side.
Deep breath inhale left arm comes up and then exhale slowly taking it over.
Inhale and then exhale.
Elbow comes closer to the floor, hand reaches closer to the ceiling and to the side.
And again, ideally, your hand and your gaze is up at your hand.
If it hurts your neck you can keep your head center even to the floor.
Deep breath inhale lift.
Exhale stretching a little bit deeper.
And last breath in.
Exhale slowly when you get back to center.
Just relaxing your hands in your lap, you can close your eyes if you like, and just feeling the affects of the stretch.